[{"question": " sure.", "answer": " thank you can you believe no one between my apartment and here offered to do that for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " people  so why you all dressed up.", "answer": " oh umm mike's picking me up for a date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh yea now um how is that going, is it getting serious?", "answer": " oh i dunno i dunno, you know i mean i like him but am i ready to take my grade a loins off the meat market.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " you know i really admire your whole dating attitude, it's so healthy i'm always like is this moving to fast? is this moving to slow? where's this going?", "answer": " yea you know you are a bit of a drama queen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " but you, your so much better off you just go from guy to guy having fun and never worrying that it terns into anything serious.", "answer": " i wouldn't say never, you know there's that guy  well what about  ok well there's gotta be someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh my god you're right.", "answer": " i know and yet here you are all ready for the next date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i can't believe i never realized this before, i'm in my thirty's and never been in a long-term relationship oh my god  what's wrong with me.", "answer": " no, no, no there's nothing wrong with you i mean you don't strike me as the type of person that wants to get married anyway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " please don't cry because of me pheebs i don't know what i'm talking about, i've been divorced three times.", "answer": " least you've been married, oh my god! i wanna trade lives with ross", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " phoebe  what's wrong?", "answer": " nothing, i'm excited about our date, mike this is ross geller this is mike haaaaa", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i'm sorry i didn't catch\u009a", "answer": " its mike hanagen", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh ross geller", "answer": " hey, so are you sure your ready to go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " do you have a compact in your purse?", "answer": "  no", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey joey", "answer": " hey, this girl won't turn around and i can't tell whether she's hot or not, what do you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " joey i am not going to objectify woman with you  but if her face is as nice as her ass woah mamma.", "answer": " alright thanks, oh hey have you talked to chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " yeah he has to stay in tulsa this weekend", "answer": " how come?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " he has to work, there's some rush on the big  ah damn it one of these days i'm really gonna have to start listening when he talks about his job.", "answer": " oh why don't you fly out there and surprise him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " maybe i will go  yea will have a second honeymoon at the tulsa romana.", "answer": " oh and you know what you should bring the black see-through teddy with the attached garters.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " how do you know i have one of those?", "answer": " didn't till just now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " hot not hot  hot!", "answer": " excuse me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i said i think you're hot and now i'm embarrassed.", "answer": " oh i thought you said hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " that would've been better, i'll try that hi i'm joey.", "answer": " i'm hayley.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " look i don't usually ask out women that i meet in coffeehouses", "answer": " ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  gesundheit", "answer": " i would love to go out with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " really, great, did i actually ask you?", "answer": " no that's just where you were going i just figured that i'd help you out, you don't seem like the kind of guy that does this very a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " ha!", "answer": "  seriously gunther you should see someone about that cold, if it gets much worse you could die!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " so how'd the date go?", "answer": " well it was awful every time i thought about what you said i started crying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " so he hasn't called?", "answer": " would you call this girl?  thanks-fo-r-a-love-ly-even-ing", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " now i feel terrible this is all my fault.", "answer": " well you not what you should feel terrible about, this could have been my serious guy he was sweet and smart and funny. do you know how hard it is to meet a guy like that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " we are a rare breed.", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " what a great dinner.", "answer": " yeah and hey thanks again for letting me having that last piece of cake at the restaurant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  your welcome again, i'm gonna make some coffee can i get you anything?", "answer": " do you have any cake?  &gt;&gt;&gt; joey's subconscious so this is going pretty good\u009a dinner was nice, got a lot in common\u009a  victoria's secret huh we even like the same books.  oh now there's a scary painting\u009a wait a minute i think i've been scared by that painting before.  you know what this whole place look familiar i have definitely been in this apartment i know i've seen this weird plant before  awch! it did that the last time. oh my god, i've gone out with this girl before yeah we had sex on this couch and then on that chair and no\u009a no we didn't do it hear which is weird because it seems like a perfectly good place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  awch! that's why.", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  hey mike sorry to just drop by like this, can i come in?", "answer": " sure  who are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i'm ross, phoebe's friend from the coffeehouse.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah i really, really need to talk to you about something.", "answer": " ok, unless you're not gonna try to get me to join a cult are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  no", "answer": " oh it's just you have that look", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " damn super cuts!", "answer": " what's up is phoebe ok?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh no yeah, no phoebe is great, but umm i'm an idiot look right before you guys went out i accidentally got her all upset.", "answer": " that's why she was weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yes, yeah i said something stupid about her never having had a serious relationship, but you should know she is so much fun, a wonderful person please don't blow her off.", "answer": " i'm not blowing her off, i actually just got off the phone with her, were going out tomorrow night, i mean i hope that's ok with you stranger from the coffee house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well then i didn't need to bother you or the four other mike hanagens i bothered.", "answer": " hey wait wait wait wait wait! is that true what you said phoebe's never had a serious relationship?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " of course she has\u009a if she'd never had a serious relationship i'd go round broadcasting it like some unstoppable moron.", "answer": " but you did say it", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " yes, yes i did\u009a and i will also say what i'm about to say vis-&agrave;-vis the following phoebe has never had a serious relationship since her\u009a super-serious relationship with\u009a vicrum.", "answer": " vicrum?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " what that's a real name!", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " is everything all right?", "answer": " everything's great, just watching some regular television there, what a pleasant surprise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i'm gonna go freshen up ok", "answer": " ok honey\u009a that was close. -cut to rachel", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hello", "answer": " hey rach its me ok i just got the chandler's room and i caught him molesting himself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh that couldn't have been pretty\u009a but you know guys do that.", "answer": " yea well the weird part is... he was getting off to a shark attack show!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " nooooooooo!", "answer": " yes! chandler watches shark porn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " well watching sharks? are you sure that's what he was doing?", "answer": " do you know how many times i've seen him jump up like that, believe me i know what he was doing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " man sharks\u009a i always knew there was something weird about that dude. but you promised to love him no matter what.", "answer": " what means if he gets like a disease or kills someone\u009a not if he gets his jollys to jaws!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " ah! you know what honey guys are just different, they like things that we can't understand, you know i once dated this guy who wanted to pretend he was an archeologist and i was a naughty cave woman that he unfroze from a block of ice.", "answer": " eww are you talking about my bother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " yeah i didn't disguise that very well did i.", "answer": "  hey", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": "  hi", "answer": " listen to this... i went out with this girl last night and half way through our date i realized i already slept with her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " so basically you've slept with all the woman in new york and now you're just going around again.", "answer": " well that's not even the weird part\u009a i don't think she remembered sleeping with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " but you don't remember sleeping with her.", "answer": " yeah but she should remember sleeping with me i am very memorable, you guys know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " what, how do we know, we never slept with you.", "answer": " and who's fault is that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " what's the big deal, you forgot, she forgot, maybe you were having an off night", "answer": " hey! i never have an off night ok although sometimes when i'm a little bloated i don't feel very sexy but even then i'm better then most!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " honey why don't you just let it go and ask her out again.", "answer": " yeah your both so slutty you don't even remember who you've slept with, you're made for each other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " interesting\u009a all right i'll go out with her again and try to get past it  oh salt bloaty!", "answer": " joey, joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you don't think sharks are sexy do you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " it's open.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " yay!  quick thing, i went to talk to mike.", "answer": " what? wha-wha-wha-did you do ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh boy you got mad at that part. i went over there to tell him how great you are but you know me blah, blah, blah, and i ended up telling him that\u009a", "answer": " what!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " umm\u009a that you had a six year long relationship with a guy named vicrum.", "answer": " what! why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well he seemed to bum hard that you'd never been in a serious relationship.", "answer": "  if you hadn't just had a baby with my best friend i swear to lucifer a raber dog would be feasting on your danglers right now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i'm not going along with some lie you made ross, no i'm just gonna be honest with him.", "answer": " good yeah just be honest with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " i'll get it", "answer": " ok", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " uh huh yeah  there's just something umm, there's something you should know  vicrum just called.", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " so it was kind of a shock after 25 years of marriage my parents, a perfect couple getting divorced, i kinda took it the hardest cause i was the youngest.", "answer": " uh huh, sure, yeah. how can you not remember me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " how could you not remember that we slept together?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " what! when?", "answer": " i dunno!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i really, really think i would remember sleeping with you", "answer": " come on, come on, search your brain all right\u009a it was  a certain amount of time ago, i was here you were here, we had sex  here, here, here not there. anything?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " no it's not ringing any bells.", "answer": " my god woman! how many people do you have to had been with not to remember any of this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey hayley you've really gotta fix that doorknob. joey!", "answer": " ooooooooooh, i slept with you! and you obviously remember me hey! i still got it.  so were good.  i'll let myself out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " \u009aand i said vicrum you can't just call every time you get lonely you know, you, you gave up that right when you slept with rachel.", "answer": " but rachel i thought she just had a baby with ross", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " yeah well  yeah you know emma's birth certificate might say geller but her eyes say mookurgee.", "answer": " that is so wrong and on top of that his a glue sniffer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " i know but he call's and my heart goes to him. you know that bastard is one smooth talking free lance kite designer.", "answer": " i just think there's somebody better out there for you,  i mean i'm not saying me but\u009a maybe me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " and you don't have to worry about glue sniffing with me\u009a although i do smell the occasional magic marker, yeah ah anyway i just think i can make you happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ok i can't do this.", "answer": " what's wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " well there is no vicrum, ross made him up because i never really have been in a long-term relationship, i've never lived with a guy, and i've never even celebrated an anniversary so\u009a  if that's too weird for you and you wanna leave i totally understand. in fact i'll close my eye's make it less awkward  you kissed me.", "answer": " uh huh", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " so you don't think i'm a total freak", "answer": " no\u009a well look can i think your weird and also cool for telling me the truth and also wanna kiss you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i guess so, can i\u009a can i think it's cool that you kiss me and also wanna kiss you again  and umm, be a little concerned about the magic markers.", "answer": " definitely", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  this is vicrum.", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " hi honey i'm home!", "answer": " hi, how was your flight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh it was great.", "answer": " here why don't you sit down, get yourself comfortable because i\u009a  have a little surprise for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " well, well, well it must be five in tulsa because it's six o clock in ny.c!", "answer": " ok  this is how much i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  honey why am i watching a bunch of sharks swimming around.", "answer": " is this not the good part? do you want me to fast forward to something a little toothier.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " no i'm not quite sure you got the right movie that's all.", "answer": " oh well this is the only one they had at our video store, but they did have something called crocodile killers. or does it always have to be sharks?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " does what always have to be sharks.", "answer": " honey look we can do something else, do you want me to get into the tub and thrash.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " what's going on?", "answer": " sweetie it's ok, i still love you, let me be a part of this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " let me be a part of this!", "answer": " i saw what you were doing in tulsa\u009a angry sharks turn you on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no they don't", "answer": " then why were you watching them and giving yourself a treat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh my god! when you came in i switched the channel, i was just watching regular porn", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " yeah just some good old fashion girl on girl american action.", "answer": " i cannot tell you how happy that makes me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " you are an amazing wife.  no really you're amazing you were actually gonna do this for me, i mean where do you find the strength and understanding over something like that.", "answer": " im very, very drunk right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  see ordinarily i would talk to her, but my confidence is shaken did i sleep with her? did i not sleep with her?", "answer": " you know maybe this is a wake up call, about your whole dating attitude. your in your thirty's and you've never had a serious relationship and you have never been in a long term relationship, here you go from woman to woman, meaningless experience to meaningless experience never even worrying that it doesn't tern into anything serious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}]